<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Softlockup on SoftLockup</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Softlockup on SoftLockup</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 08:58:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Track Registry Key Modifications Using Process Monitor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Windows/How-to-Track-Registry-Key-Modifications-Using-Process-Monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 12:16:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Windows/How-to-Track-Registry-Key-Modifications-Using-Process-Monitor/</guid>
      <description>How to Track Registry Key Modifications Using Process Monitor&#xD;Modifying registry keys is a common operation that can be performed by both system and user processes. But what happens when a registry key value changes unexpectedly, leading to system behavior that’s hard to diagnose? Knowing exactly which process modified a registry key can be invaluable in system administration and debugging scenarios. One powerful tool that can help you identify such changes in real-time is Sysinternals Process Monitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Hyper-V Works, High Level Overview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Windows/how-hyper-v-works-high-level-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:16:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Windows/how-hyper-v-works-high-level-overview/</guid>
      <description>How Hyper-V Works, High Level Overview&#xD;Hyper-V stands as Microsoft’s first standalone hypervisor, offering extensive support for the x86-64 architecture. It has established its own space in the virtualization market, going toe-to-toe with competitors like VMware ESXi, Xen, and KVM. One of its distinct advantages is its native integration with Microsoft-centric environments.&#xA;Contrary to many Type 2 hypervisors that function atop an existing operating system, Hyper-V is a Type 1 hypervisor that interacts directly with the hardware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Place Upgrade Your Windows Server Azure VM: Step by Step Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Cloud/windows-server-azure-vm-in-place-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:16:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Cloud/windows-server-azure-vm-in-place-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>In Place Upgrade Your Windows Server Azure VM: Step by Step Guide&#xD;Upgrading your Windows Server Azure VM to a newer version can seem daunting, but with the right steps, it can be a smooth process. This guide will walk you through a step-by-step process, complete with visuals, to upgrade your Windows VM in Azure, for instance, from WS 2016 to 2019.&#xA;Prerequisites for a Successful Upgrade&#xD;Before diving into the upgrade, ensure the following prerequisites are met:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Kernel - Deep Dive into Soft/Hard Lockups</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Linux/Kernel/softlockup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Linux/Kernel/softlockup/</guid>
      <description>Introduction&#xD;Kernel Watchdog&#xD;According to Linux Kernel Documentation, the Linux kernel can act as a watchdog to detect both soft and hard lockups.&#xA;The Linux Kernel Watchdog is a mechanism that monitors the system for both soft and hard lockups. It is designed to detect when a CPU is stuck in a loop and unable to make progress. When a soft lockup is detected, the watchdog will print a warning message to the system log.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Reboot Quick Analyzer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Linux/linuxrebootcheck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/SystemAdministration/Linux/linuxrebootcheck/</guid>
      <description>What is Linux Boot/Shutdown Quick-Analyzer and why do you need it?&#xD;The Linux Boot/Shutdown Quick-Analyzer is a Python script that analyzes Linux boot and shutdown logs.&#xA;It makes it easy to find boot and shutdown events in system logs, providing information such as the number of boot and shutdown events, along with the timestamp, filename, and line number for each event.&#xA;How to run it&#xD;You need to have Python 3 installed on your machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/authors/John-Doe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/authors/John-Doe/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m jhon doe</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
